=The Origin of Eternity=
= أصل الخلود =
=Episode 16=
= الحلقة 16 =
How vicious of him!
يا له من شراسة!
The truth is revealed.
تم الكشف عن الحقيقة.
I can rest in peace, then.
يمكنني أن أرقد بسلام ، إذن.
No.
لا.
I...
أنا...
I won't allow you to die.
لن أسمح لك بالموت.
Since I was young, my mother used to tell me
منذ أن كنت صغيرة ، كانت والدتي تخبرني
that "staying beside the monarch"
أن "البقاء بجانب الملك"
"is like staying beside a tiger."
"مثل البقاء بجانب نمر."
I'm born in the royal family,
ولدت في العائلة المالكة ،
I shouldn't have wistful thinking
لا ينبغي أن يكون لدي تفكير حزين
and never give my heart to someone.
ولا أعطي قلبي لشخص ما.
I always keep myself in perfect check
أنا دائما أتحقق من نفسي
when I'm in front of my father.
عندما أكون أمام والدي.
I have never
لم يسبق لي
made a mistake.
ارتكبت خطأ.
♪I turn into the gentle mist and caress your face♪
♪ أتحول إلى ضباب لطيف وأداعب وجهك
However, for the first time,
ومع ذلك ، ولأول مرة ،
I have a desire
لدي رغبة
because of you.
بسببك.
I was thinking
كنت افكر
to give you my pure sincerity
لأعطيك إخلاصي الخالص
and receive yours in return.
والحصول على لك في المقابل.
♪Journeying through the vast time♪
السفر عبر الزمن الشاسع
♪We stop at the end of the reincarnation cycle♪
♪ نتوقف عند نهاية دورة التناسخ ♪
I always feel smart.
أشعر دائمًا بالذكاء.
But now seems
ولكن يبدو الآن
I'm a stupid fool.
أنا أحمق غبي.
I'm such a fool.
أنا مجنون.
Bai Ze.
باي زي.
Do you really love me?
هل حقا تحبني؟
Love?
حب؟
♪For another thousand years♪
♪ لألف سنة أخرى ♪
Now that we have come this far,
الآن وقد وصلنا إلى هذا الحد ،
do you think
هل تعتقد
"love" is a thing for us?
"الحب" شيء بالنسبة لنا؟
No.
لا.
Not anymore.
ليس بعد الآن.
I was outfoxed
لقد تفوقت علي
by the Third Prince.
من قبل الأمير الثالث.
I truly like you.
أنا معجب بك حقًا.
I will make amends.
سوف أقوم بالتعويض.
I definitely will.
أنا بالتأكيد سوف.
No need.
لا حاجة.
♪I turn into the snow to freeze fickleness♪
♪ ألتفت إلى الثلج لتجميد التقلبات ♪
My love for you
حبي لك
is over.
انتهى.
♪Journeying through the vast time♪
السفر عبر الزمن الشاسع
♪We stop at the end of the reincarnation cycle♪
♪ نتوقف عند نهاية دورة التناسخ ♪
Bai Ze.
باي زي.
♪The time was fleeting away before the iris wilted♪
كان الوقت يمر بعيدًا قبل أن تذبل القزحية ♪
Men!
رجال!
Send the imperial physician here.
أرسل الطبيب الإمبراطوري هنا.
Bai Ze.
باي زي.
♪I couldn't free myself from the entanglement of love♪
♪ لم أستطع تحرير نفسي من ورطة الحب ♪
♪I didn't want to see a tearful farewell♪
♪ لم أرغب في رؤية وداع باكي ♪
♪I was obsessed with the love of the past♪
♪ كنت مهووسًا بحب الماضي
♪If only I could first see you in the next life♪
♪ لو كان بإمكاني رؤيتك أولاً في الحياة التالية ♪
♪I wish we could be together again♪
♪ أتمنى أن نكون معًا مرة أخرى ♪
♪For another thousand years♪
♪ لألف سنة أخرى ♪
It has been one day and one night.
لقد كان يوما وليلة.
How come his body still feels feverish?
كيف لا يزال جسده يشعر بالحمى؟
♪For another thousand years♪
♪ لألف سنة أخرى ♪
Bai Ze.
باي زي.
I believe in you.
إنني أ ثق بك.
Are you willing
هل أنت على استعداد
to stay with me?
للبقاء معي؟
You're awake.
انت مستيقظ.
Bring the imperial physician here.
أحضر الطبيب الإمبراطوري هنا.
Bai Ze.
باي زي.
I'm to blame.
انا الملام.
You're of noble identity.
أنت ذو هوية نبيلة.
No need to bow down to me.
لا حاجة للانحناء لي.
I'm just a commoner.
أنا مجرد عامة.
I don't deserve this.
أنا لا أستحق هذا.
Please don't turn me away.
من فضلك لا تبعدني.
I'm willing
أرغب
to take care of you.
من اجل الاعتناء بك.
If so,
لو ذلك،
please send me back to the relay station.
من فضلك أرسلني مرة أخرى إلى محطة الترحيل.
This will be
هذا سيكون
to greatest grace for me.
لأعظم نعمة بالنسبة لي.
I'm sorry to let you down.
أنا آسف أن خذلتك.
I will make it up to you.
سأعوضك عن ذلك.
Do you have any wishes?
هل لديك امنيات؟
I will grant your wish
سأمنح أمنيتك
in my power.
في قوتي.
No need.
لا حاجة.
I swear to heaven.
اقسم بالجنة.
I only have one request.
لدي طلب واحد فقط.
Your Majesty,
جلالة الملك ،
please allow me to return to my home.
من فضلك اسمح لي بالعودة إلى منزلي.
No, you can't.
لا ، لا يمكنك ذلك.
During your days in prison,
خلال أيامك في السجن ،
the emperor of the Ling Empire
إمبراطور إمبراطورية لينغ
has appointed Third Prince
عين الأمير الثالث
as the new Crown Prince.
ولي العهد الجديد.
This can't be true.
هذا لا يمكن أن يكون صحيحا.
My parents made a promise to me before.
لقد وعدني والداي من قبل.
Besides, Father is in perfect health.
الى جانب ذلك ، الأب في صحة كاملة.
How could this be?
كيف يكون ذلك؟
Unless...
إلا إذا...
Unless they thought I wouldn't be coming back again.
إلا إذا اعتقدوا أنني لن أعود مرة أخرى.
The news of you
اخباركم
taking me into the harem
يأخذني إلى الحريم
has been circulated wide and fast in the Ling Empire.
تم تداوله على نطاق واسع وسريع في إمبراطورية لينغ.
Before, the Third Prince requested my assistance
قبل ذلك ، طلب الأمير الثالث مساعدتي
in his letter
في رسالته
to help him become the Crown Prince
لمساعدته في أن يصبح ولي العهد
by confining you here.
من خلال حصرك هنا.
He promised
لقد وعد
he would submit to the Sheng Empire.
سيخضع لإمبراطورية شنغ.
I did something wrong
لقد فعلت شيئا خاطئا
to keep you here.
لإبقائك هنا.
You did this for the sake of the Great Sheng.
لقد فعلت هذا من أجل Great Sheng.
You did nothing wrong.
أنت لم تفعل شيئًا خاطئًا.
Lord Yong died
مات اللورد يونغ
because of the trick
بسبب الحيلة
of the Third Prince.
الأمير الثالث.
I have had my punishment.
لقد كان لي عقابي.
Bai Ze.
باي زي.
I know I let you down.
أعلم أنني خذلتك.
Will you
سوف تفعل
be my consort?
كن رفيقي؟
You're not the Crown Prince of the Ling Empire now.
أنت لست ولي عهد إمبراطورية لينغ الآن.
You don't have to consider Ling's interest.
ليس عليك التفكير في مصلحة لينغ.
Please be my consort.
من فضلك كن رفيقي.
Sheng is more powerful than Ling.
شنغ أقوى من لينغ.
If we were to join hands,
إذا كان علينا أن نتعاون ،
we will rule the world
سنحكم العالم
and create a prosperous world.
وخلق عالم مزدهر.
Consort?
القرين؟
You have colluded with my brother
لقد تواطأت مع أخي
to ruin my future and I can't return home anymore.
لتدمير مستقبلي ولا يمكنني العودة إلى المنزل بعد الآن.
Yet you're making such a beautiful promise
ومع ذلك ، أنت تقدم مثل هذا الوعد الجميل
to take me as your consort.
لأخذني كرفيق لك.
Do you want me to enter the harem with a grateful heart?
هل تريدين دخول الحريم بقلب ممتن؟
I truly love you.
أحبك بصدق.
I want to spend the rest of my life with you.
اريد ان اقضي بقية حياتي معك.
Truly?
حقا؟
Does such a thing exist
هل يوجد شيء كهذا
between us?
بيننا؟
Your Majesty, please allow me
جلالة الملك ، من فضلك اسمح لي
to move back to the relay station.
للعودة إلى محطة الترحيل.
♪Wandered off from the crowd♪
تجول بعيدًا عن الحشد ♪
♪As more wonderful things await♪
♪ كما تنتظر المزيد من الأشياء الرائعة
♪A sunset from the past resurfaced♪
انعكاس غروب الشمس من الماضي
♪Thousands of sailboats drifted in the sea of clouds♪
جرفت آلاف المراكب الشراعية في بحر السحب
♪And docked at different piers♪
♪ ورست على أرصفة مختلفة ♪
♪Only the catkin willow and my graying hair remained♪
فقط صفصاف القطة وشعري الشيب بقي
♪Let's take on♪
♪ لنأخذ
♪Another year♪
♪ سنة أخرى ♪
♪I traveled alone toward daytime as I waved aside the night♪
سافرت لوحدي في النهار بينما كنت ألوح جانباً في الليل
♪The tapping rain♪
مطر التنصت ♪
♪Awakened the sorrow♪
أيقظ الحزن
♪I'm crying out in loneliness amid pandemonium♪
♪ أنا أبكي في عزلة وسط الهرج والمرج
♪I endured countless ordeals from worldly entanglement♪
لقد تحملت محن لا حصر لها من التشابك الدنيوي ♪
♪Knowing how difficult things are for the first time♪
معرفة مدى صعوبة الأمور لأول مرة ♪
♪After you overcome the vicissitudes of life♪
بعد أن تتغلب على تقلبات الحياة
♪Only then do you understand the fickleness of the world♪
"عندها فقط تفهم تقلب العالم"
♪I wanted to enjoy the years but it turned into a disaster overnight♪
♪ أردت الاستمتاع بالسنوات لكنها تحولت إلى كارثة بين عشية وضحاها
♪Knowing that I can't turn back time♪
♪ مع العلم أنني لا أستطيع العودة بالزمن ♪
♪You would not be intoxicated by sorrow♪
لن تسكر بالحزن
♪Until you were embroiled in love♪
حتى تتورط في الحب ♪
♪I wanted to enjoy the years but it turned into a disaster overnight♪
♪ أردت الاستمتاع بالسنوات لكنها تحولت إلى كارثة بين عشية وضحاها
♪Knowing that I can't turn back time♪
♪ مع العلم أنني لا أستطيع العودة بالزمن ♪
♪You would not be intoxicated by sorrow♪
لن تسكر بالحزن
♪Until you were embroiled in love♪
حتى تتورط في الحب ♪